Ivan Vesković

Junior front end developer



CONTACTS

062/208-646



i.veskovic92@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/ivan-veskov ic-8b1573127/



Belgrade, Serbia



ivanveskovic.github.io/Portfolio/



github.com/IvanVeskovic

SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

Ajax

Flexbox & CSS Grid

Git & GitHub

React

SCSS & BEM

Bootstrap

LANGUAGES

Serbian





English





HOBBIES











ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Ivan, I'm a junior Front End Developer based in Belgrade. I describe myself as a courious and persistent team player. Currently I'm working as an associate in power engineering "Infrastruktura Zeleznice Srbije", but I set myself the task of returning to the path I started several years ago. I strive for constant learning of new technologies.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2017

Information technology

The Higher Education Technical School of

Professional Studies

Novi Sad

2007-2011

Computer technician

High Tehnical School Kosjerić

Kosjerić

Other sources

Udemy, Youtube, FreeCodeCamp etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - Present Independent Technical Associate

Infrastruktura Železnice Srbije

Maintenance of railway power plants creating working plans and procurement

plans.

Belgrade

2019 - Present Wordpress e-commerce content and website maintenance.

Leo Commerce

Updating books and other sections.

Belgrade

PROJECTS

PSD to HTML

Converting website from PSD in Zeplin to HTML

Weather APP

HTML, Bootstrap, API and JavaScript

Cocktail APP

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API, Local Storage.

Mobile Web Shop

Html, SASS, FlexBox, JavaScript.